hostingcontroller.com 2011-06-30

# Hosting Controller - Privacy Policy - Server Control panel - Dedicated Server Control Panel - Hosting Management Solution - Windows Automation tool

---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---  
  |  |   
---  
  
Hosting Controller is a wholly owned subsidiary of Hosting Controller, Inc., a Canadian Corporation. Hosting Controller is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read the complete HostingController.com privacy statement.   
Our corporate postal address is: 

> **Hosting Controller Inc.**  
>  5811 Cooney Road, Suite 305  
>  Richmond, BC, V6X 3M1  
>  Canada
> 
> Our offices can be reached via e-mail at [sales@hostingcontroller.com](mailto:sales@hostingcontroller.com) or via telephone at +1 (604) 227-0272.   
  
**Email Privacy Policy**  
We have created this email privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy and the protection of your information. 

We only collect the e-mail addresses of those who voluntarily submit them to us by making postings to our discussion groups, ordering from us online, registering for downloads, etc.   
We will never share, sell, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance permission or unless ordered by a court of law. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you.   
  
Postal and Telephone Privacy Policy   
Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online. They also may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you supply us with your postal address you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events.  
Web Site Security  
Hosting Controller is equipped with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL protocol enables encrypted, authenticated communications across the Internet. SSL uses public key encryption mechanisms, one of the strongest encryption methods available to protect data sent over the Internet. SSL provides 3 important services, all using public key techniques: Privacy, Authentication, and Message Integrity. Customer information sent is not discernible to anyone except the recipient.

When accessing our online store using a secure browser, one can feel secure transmitting credit card or other confidential information sent over   
  
**Web Site Visits**  
  
Each time you visit Hosting Controller Web Site, our server automatically recognizes and logs your IP address. An IP address is basically the address of the computer making a request to our web server. No personal information or detail is obtained in this data interchange.

At Hosting Controller logged IP addresses are periodically reviewed and analyzed in an effort to monitor, maintain, and effectively improve our Web site. This information is retained for no other purpose and is not shared outside of Hosting Controller.

During a Web site visit, we may ask a customer for contact information (email address, telephone number, fax number and addresses for billing). This information is collected on a voluntary basis—and only with customer approval.

Hosting Controller Web site contains links to other web sites. HC does not control or take responsibility for personal information collected on these sites nor is HC responsible for the accuracy or the content of these sites.   
  
**Note:** We reserve the right to make changes to our privacy policy at any time without prior notification.  

|  |   
|  |   
|  |   
|  |   
|  Home | HC8 Overview | HC Enterprise Modules | HC8 Features | Privacy Policy | License Agreement | Site Map | © Hosting Controller 1998 - 2011  
---|---  
  
Founded in 1999, Hosting Controller is a complete hosting automation solution for web hosts and cloud based service providers. It allows them to manage both Windows & Linux servers simultaneously as part of a single cluster. In addition to shared hosts, HC offers a full solution suite for hosted Enterprise Applications creating a shared multi-tenant environment for automatic provisioning of Exchange 2007/2010, BlackBerry, SharePoint, OCS and Dynamics CRM. It also offers a full automation solution for Infrastructure and Virtualization providers offering virtualized partitions on both Windows and Linux based servers through Hyper-V technology for Windows & Xen Hypervisor technology for Linux! Hosting Controller Inc. is based in Richmond, BC, Canada and has customers in 125 countries worldwide.
